These exercises will bulletproof your core. Start with standing posterior plate twists
to get obliques that pop. Turning strong abs but neglecting the obliques is like building
a house with only two walls, so for more load I like to use barbell side bends. If that's
too much, switch the bar for kettlebells and they turn into Chinese side bends. Next is
ab roller. It's a classic for a reason, but if you made this mistake, you'll get nothing
out of it. Instead of arching your back or bending your arms, you'll want to keep the
arms straight and round your back for that eight-pack aesthetic. Next is like the crunch
is older, more powerful brother. Keep the feet elevated and crunch into a V with your
entire body. V-ups are great if you want to hit the lower abs some more or have some extra
time in the gym. All of these exercises came straight from our training at Peak Strength
that allows you to make a personalized program based on your specific needs like experience
level, what sport you're training for, equipment you have access to. It tells you what to do
down to every detail. You give it your feedback on how hard that set was and it'll adjust
your weight accordingly for the next set. So if you need any kind of help with your
training, go to the story, click the link and get a free week of training. These exercises